questions = [
    {
        "question":"Which is a hardwood?",
        "correctAnswer":"Oak",
        "answer0":"Pine",
        "answer1":"Red Cedar",
        "answer2":"Chipboard"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a hardwood?",
        "correctAnswer":"Mahogany",
        "answer0":"Spruce",
        "answer1":"Pine",
        "answer2":"MDF"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a hardwood?",
        "correctAnswer":"Beech",
        "answer0":"Red Cedar",
        "answer1":"Plywood",
        "answer2":"Spruce"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a hardwood?",
        "correctAnswer":"Teak",
        "answer0":"Chipboard",
        "answer1":"Blockboard",
        "answer2":"Pine"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a hardwood?",
        "correctAnswer":"Balsa",
        "answer0":"Spruce",
        "answer1":"Plywood",
        "answer2":"Red Cedar"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a softwood?",
        "correctAnswer":"Pine",
        "answer0":"Oak",
        "answer1":"Plywood",
        "answer2":"Teak"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a softwood?",
        "correctAnswer":"Red Cedar",
        "answer0":"Balsa",
        "answer1":"Mahogany",
        "answer2":"Beech"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a softwood?",
        "correctAnswer":"Spruce",
        "answer0":"MDF",
        "answer1":"Teak",
        "answer2":"Chipboard"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a manufactured board?",
        "correctAnswer":"Plywood",
        "answer0":"Teak",
        "answer1":"Spruce",
        "answer2":"Pine"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a manufactured board?",
        "correctAnswer":"Flexi-Ply",
        "answer0":"Oak",
        "answer1":"Mahogany",
        "answer2":"Red Cedar"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a manufactured board?",
        "correctAnswer":"Marine Ply",
        "answer0":"Teak",
        "answer1":"Balsa",
        "answer2":"Pine"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a manufactured board?",
        "correctAnswer":"MDF",
        "answer0":"Pine",
        "answer1":"Balsa",
        "answer2":"Spruce"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a manufactured board?",
        "correctAnswer":"Blockboard",
        "answer0":"Mahogany",
        "answer1":"Teak",
        "answer2":"Beech"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which is a manufactured board?",
        "correctAnswer":"Chipboard",
        "answer0":"Balsa",
        "answer1":"Oak",
        "answer2":"Spruce"
    }
]